today I will teach you
how to sell water in the crazy desert
I will use a clipboard
a pen
all those waters I bought without ice
because ice cream is expensive
the question is
how am i going to sell water without ice here on the beach
hand
all right people
I'm doing research for my master's degree
two little questions very quickly
can be
from channel two to channel five
I don't know if you are aware
the price of the water being sold on the beach
it's an average of ten reais who find it cheap or expensive
dear to you
which of these prices below
you would pay in fair price water
five reais
seven real or ten real
five everyone five
my water is priceless
you put whatever price you want on water
and you said
five reais
it's here for you
this is the marketing i do
to connect with people
experienced exactly this
three more
caramba
look at this people
speaks beauty troop
thank you
couple all right
we accept pix too
You said five reais,
right?
five reais
is to buy water
and here i accept pix too
leave water for you here
it's great
I trust you
goodbye all the best to you
bye bye
make a lot of sales here to get more water
ah heat of hell
three and a half liters is coming out at that price
is taking pot
thank you bye
bye bye yalikipitia
five reais
and for you who
knows ha ha ha
oh man
so i'm talking to you bro
I just sold it to a bunch of good people here
because of marketing bro
so that's it
when we create experience ahead
and does not put the product
we are more interesting than interested
worth it thanks bro worth it
didn't want to buy because my water is hot
not everyone is prepared for a visionary guy
I have thirty days to set up my business.
fight for today
tomorrow we are together valeu
ok uhuru
So